Class of 1885 Records, 1881-1999
Smith College Archives
Class of 1885 Records
1881-1999
Smith College. Class of 1885.
RG 80 UUID:349103b2-76b7-4594-bc8e-f920d46caee7
6 boxes (2.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, photo albums, letters, correspondence, newspaper and magazine clippings, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1885.
The Class of 1885 was the seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1885 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1885. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, letters, correspondence, newspaper and magazine clippings, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1885.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1885 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1885: Class Colors 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 1)
- Class of 1885: Commencement 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 2)
- Class of 1885: Commencement Music 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 3)
- Class of 1885: Commencement Poem 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 4)
- Class of 1885: Groups 1883, 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 5)
- Class of 1885: Ivy Day 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 6)
- Class of 1885: Class Letters undated (Box 1419, Folder 7)
- Class of 1885: Garfield Memorial Day 1881 (Box 1419, Folder 8)
- Class of 1885: Reunions 1910, 1915 (Box 1419, Folder 9)
- Class of 1885: Reunion Photographs 1925, 1930, 1935, 1940, 1949, 1950, undated (Box 1419, Folder 10)
- Class of 1885: Senior Reception 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 11)
- Class of 1885: Sophomore Reception 1881 (Box 1419, Folder 12)
- Class of 1885: Songs undated (Box 1419, Folder 13)
- Class of 1885: Class Supper 1885 (Box 1419, Folder 14)
- Class of 1885: Aldrich, Mary Louise (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 1)
- Class of 1885: Bartley, Helen Preston 1885 (Box 1420, Folder 2)
- Class of 1885: Brewster, Katharine Grant (Correspondence) 1883-86 (Box 1420, Folder 3)
- Class of 1885: Brewster, Katharine Grant (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 4)
- Class of 1885: Browning, Sarah Perry (Photographs, etc) 1885, 1892, 1900-07, 1909 (Box 1420, Folder 5)
- Class of 1885: Calkins, Mary Whiton 1885, 1888, 1906, 1909-11, 1916-17, 1919, 1921, 1923, 1925-31, 1937 (Box 1420, Folder 6)
- Class of 1885: Capen, Anne undated (Box 1420, Folder 7)
- Class of 1885: Cheever, Elizabeth (Letters, etc) 1885, undated (Box 1420, Folder 8)
- Class of 1885: Chickering, Frances (Photographs) (Box 1420, Folder 9)
- Class of 1885: Clark, Annie Louise (Photographs, etc) 1890, undated (Box 1420, Folder 10)
- Class of 1885: Clarke, Ellen Williston (Letters, etc) 1885, 1915, 1924 (Box 1420, Folder 11)
- Class of 1885: Clough, Nathalie Duley (Photographs, etc) 1935, 1938, 1942, 1946, 1948, 1979, undated (Box 1420, Folder 12)
- Class of 1885: Coffin, Elizabeth Marshall 1889 (Box 1420, Folder 13)
- Class of 1885: Crocker, Augusta Percival undated (Box 1420, Folder 14)
- Class of 1885: Crouse, Martha Parsons (Photographs) 1885 (Box 1420, Folder 15)
- Class of 1885: Cutler, Anna Alice (Box 1420, Folder 16)
- Class of 1885: Dean, Emma Jane 1911, 1913, 1927, undated (Box 1420, Folder 17)
- Class of 1885: De Golyer, Nellie Louise (Correspondence) 1885-86 (Box 1420, Folder 18)
- Class of 1885: De Golyer, Nellie Louise (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 19)
- Class of 1885: Derby, Alice Hubbard 1945 (Box 1420, Folder 20)
- Class of 1885: Eager, Louise undated (Box 1420, Folder 21)
- Class of 1885: Emory, Carrie Jane (Correspondence) 1884-87 (Box 1420, Folder 22)
- Class of 1885: Emory, Carrie Jane (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 23)
- Class of 1885: Fisher, Mary Preston (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 24)
- Class of 1885: Fletcher, Mabel (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 25)
- Class of 1885: Franklin, Ruth Barker (Photographs, etc) 1936, 1953, 1957, undated (Box 1420, Folder 26)
- Class of 1885: Gould, Jennie Etta undated (Box 1420, Folder 27)
- Class of 1885: Greene, Anna Edith (Correspondence) 1883-84, 1886 (Box 1420, Folder 28)
- Class of 1885: Greene, Anna Edith (Photographs) 1885 (Box 1420, Folder 29)
- Class of 1885: Greenough, Jeanie Grace 1886, undated (Box 1420, Folder 30)
- Class of 1885: Haines, Mary Caroline (Photographs) 1886, undated (Box 1420, Folder 31)
- Class of 1885: Hallock, Nellie Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 32)
- Class of 1885: Hamilton, Caroline Frances 1896, 1919-21, 1923, 1931-32, 1934, 1944, undated (Box 1420, Folder 33)
- Class of 1885: Hardy, Mary Chapman (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 34)
- Class of 1885: Haskell, Evelyn Belle undated (Box 1420, Folder 35)
- Class of 1885: Hay, Isabel Bancroft (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 36)
- Class of 1885: Hayward, Grace (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 37)
- Class of 1885: Hobart, Bessie Jewett (Photographs) undated (Box 1420, Folder 38)
- Class of 1885: Hungerford, Charlotte Elizabeth undated (Box 1420, Folder 39)
- Class of 1885: Johnson, Mary A. (Photographs, etc) 1881, 1884, 1889, undated (Box 1421, Folder 1)
- Class of 1885: Knox, Mary Fake (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1421, Folder 2)
- Class of 1885: Laundon, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 3)
- Class of 1885: Lawrence, Marion undated (Box 1421, Folder 4)
- Class of 1885: McCloud, Lucy Carter 1948, 1998-99, undated (Box 1421, Folder 5)
- Class of 1885: McCloud, Lucy Carter (Class Notes, Bible) 1884 (Box 1421, Folder 6)
- Class of 1885: McFarland, Clara Mandana (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 7)
- Class of 1885: Mead, Anna Leocadie (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 8)
- Class of 1885: Mercereau, Grace Edith (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 9)
- Class of 1885: Munson, Maud Antoinette (Correspondence) 1883-86, undated (Box 1421, Folder 10)
- Class of 1885: Natt, Josephine Agnes (Correspondence) 1883-86, undated (Box 1421, Folder 11)
- Class of 1885: Natt, Josephine Agnes (Photographs, etc) 1935-36, undated (Box 1421, Folder 12)
- Class of 1885: Nye, Caroline Huckins (Correspondence) undated (Box 1421, Folder 13)
- Class of 1885: Nye, Caroline Huckins (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 14)
- Class of 1885: O'Brion, Virgie Inez undated (Box 1421, Folder 15)
- Class of 1885: Parsons, Amelia Olmstead (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1421, Folder 16)
- Class of 1885: Ray, Anna Chapin (Photographs, etc) 1884, 1931, undated (Box 1421, Folder 17)
- Class of 1885: Richardson, Alice Maude (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 18)
- Class of 1885: Riker, Ida Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 19)
- Class of 1885: Smith, Mary Whitall (Photographs, etc) 1884-85, 1931, 1948, 1959, 1965, 1979, 1980, 1984, undated (Box 1421, Folder 20)
- Class of 1885: Soule, Margaret Howard (Photographs) 1882, undated (Box 1421, Folder 21)
- Class of 1885: Spring, Jennie Sweetser undated (Box 1421, Folder 22)
- Class of 1885: Stetson, Clara (Correspondence) 1885-86 (Box 1421, Folder 23)
- Class of 1885: Stetson, Clara (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 24)
- Class of 1885: Swazey, Helen Clark (Photographs) 1881, undated (Box 1421, Folder 25)
- Class of 1885: Tait, Flora Chapman (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 26)
- Class of 1885: Talcott, Elizabeth Hannah undated (Box 1421, Folder 27)
- Class of 1885: Taylor, Lucy Burgess undated (Box 1421, Folder 28)
- Class of 1885: (ex-1885) Underwood, Mary Louise 1895-99, 1901, 1905-07, 1910-13, 1916-20 (Box 1421, Folder 29)
- Class of 1885: Walker, Gertrude Annie (Box 1421, Folder 30)
- Class of 1885: Watson, Nellie Jane (Photographs) undated (Box 1421, Folder 31)
- Class of 1885: Whitcomb, Carrie May undated (Box 1421, Folder 32)
- Class of 1885: Woodbury, Georgiana Smith (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1421, Folder 33)
- Class of 1885: Woodward, Katherine Sheperd (Box 1421, Folder 34)
- Class of 1885: Cheever, Elizabeth Bancroft (Photo Album) undated (Box 1422)
- Class of 1885: Clark, Annie Louise (Photo Albums) undated (Box 1423)
- Class of 1885: Hardy, Mary Chapman (Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1424)